I'm not sure if I can do it.
Sorry to keep you waiting. It's about to
start.
Hello! Project 2023 Summer City Circuit
is over!
This time it was a short tour, but thank
you to everyone who came.
Juice Juice will be on sale from
September 23rd to the 13th.
Please come and see us!
Thank you for watching!
Juice Juice will start the 10th
Anniversary Concert Tour 2023 Juice Tree
from September 23rd.
This is an autumn tour, but Juice Tree
is a combination of juice and history.
I think it's a set list that makes you
feel the history of Juice Juice.
I think it's a content that will be fun
for those who come to the concert every
time.
I hope you look forward to it!
And BEYOND will be on the Japan Iconic
Music Festival 2023 on September 23rd.
BEYOND has always said that we want to
be active beyond the sea from the
beginning of our formation.
I'm very happy to be able to perform
overseas.
I'm very excited because it's my first
time going abroad.
Please come and see us!
And on September 9th and 10th, the 25th
Anniversary Concert of Hello! Project
will be held.
Hello! Project members and seniors will
also be there.
It's going to be a very luxurious and
special concert.
How about you, Risa?
I haven't met the members yet, so I'd
like to say hello to them and perform on
stage together.
I don't know what kind of performance it
will be at this point, but I'm looking
forward to it!
Please watch this video!
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
Please subscribe to my channel!
But it's painful
An even angle piece
The memories are dazzling
Shine far away
Search for it
A new energy
A future that's too big
Are you ready?
Before it's too late
Goodbye
It's a door-opening
It doesn't matter what it is
Each of us will go to make it come true
with love
It's okay, I'm brave, so I'll do it
But I'll still do my best, for the sake
of our love
Courage is my life
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
Tomorrow, we can become anything we
want!
I won't look at you
With regret
It's okay
I will not give up
I don't feel like running away
But still
For the sake of something, until the day
we meet
I'm gonna be alright
I'll choose my heartbeats
From now on, I'll meet you again
La la la la la la la la la la la
Mmm...
Don't be lonely
Smile and shoot and
One love love
Stay in love
I love you boy
Each of us has love
We're going to make it come true
I'm so in love
I'm not a coward
But still, I'll do my best
For the sake of love
I'll have courage
Courage is my life
La la la la la
It's my life
Come on!
La La La
Something good happened today.
I'm Irie Risato from Juice Juice.
I'm Hanaste from Beyonds.
We're going to talk about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so
let's answer them quickly.
I'll do my best.
What are you preparing for your first
overseas performance?
It's my first overseas performance, so
I'm asking the members what they need.
I went to the fireworks show in a yukata
with the members.
I'm into taking pictures of the sky.
I'm wearing a black and brown outfit.
What is the song that you think has a
great story?
It's a song called Boy with Glasses.
I'm asking the members what they need.
I'm learning what I need to live.
I'm learning what I need to use this
outlet.
Have you ever been to the fireworks
show?
I haven't.
I had a chance to go, but I couldn't
because of the coronavirus.
I want to go soon.
Did you wear a yukata because you were
impressed by the summer?
I wore a yukata.
I didn't have a chance to wear a yukata
in private.
I was happy to wear a yukata with Yoha
and Hane.
It's wonderful.
I wanted to be there.
I'm glad.
I'll ask you a question later.
ذا başlıyorum!!!
It's my life!
It doesn't matter what happens next week
We are each different
Tsubaki Factory
Yuuki! It's my life!
On sale September 27
It doesn't matter who you are
Deceive me perfectly
Tsubaki Factory
It doesn't matter
On sale September 27
Hello! Stay!
Next, I'd like to ask Risa-chan a
question.
I'll do my best!
When did you feel like you had won?
When I was hungry but I didn't eat and
just slept.
Wow.
When did you feel like you had become a
member of the 11 members after 3 months?
When I had to shoot and when I had to
change my formation.
What food do you like?
Onigiri and miso soup.
Risa-chan has a cute look and a powerful
voice with a gap.
What do you think of when you perform?
I just enjoy the live performance.
Which song do you want to perform in the
history of Hello! Project?
I want to perform the song called,
''Moshimo'' by Moby Kimbap.
Wow.
Moshimo by Moby Kimbap? That's a good
song.
My fans often say that they want to see
me perform.
I often get a part to say my lines.
I want to try it someday.
I love your cute lines.
I want to see you perform.
I want to see you perform someday.
I will do it someday.
When did you feel like you had become a
member of the 11 members?
How do you feel when you talk with Mifu-
chan?
She is a great talker.
Is that so?
Even when we are together, we can't stop
talking.
She talks to me a lot.
I often dance with her before the
rehearsal.
I don't have a part in the dance, but I
often teach her.
You are a great senior.
Thank you.
Hello! Project will continue.
​​​ ​Thanks for watching!​ ​​
I'm Miyabi Natsuyaki.
Hello Kitchen has begun!
This time, we have this member with us.
I'm Hiroyumi Anjou.
I don't usually cook, so I'm a little
nervous.
But I'll do my best!
Thank you!
Thank you, teacher!
What are we going to make today?
Today, we're making pork piccata.
Yes, pork piccata!
I don't usually ask, but how about you,
Ayama-chan?
I don't know either, so please teach me!
Pork piccata is an Italian dish.
It's called piccata.
I think it's eaten in Europe now.
When I was in France, I used to serve it
as a side dish or for lunch.
I see.
It's like a thin pork cutlet without
bread crumbs.
But it's more flavorful.
Because I put a lot of cheese in it.
That's great!
I love cheese!
I have Italian parmigiano.
I'll put in as much as I can.
Let's do our best!
Thank you!
Please subscribe to my channel!
What are we going to do first?
First, we're going to make a sauce.
A sauce.
It's called Garni.
It's a French sauce.
I see.
Prepare Garni.
It's kind of fancy.
It's called Garniture.
Garniture.
It's an Italian dish, but we're going to
make a sauce.
It's a French sauce called Carrot Lape.
We're going to make this.
When you were in elementary school, did
you cook with your mom?
I was cooking with my mom, but I was in
a cooking club.
What?
When you were in elementary school?
That's right.
I was cooking with my friends.
You can do it, right?
I'm so excited.
I want to be able to make it and go
home.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
This is almost the same.
It's the same with pickles.
Put the vegetables in here.
Carrots are easy to feel the salt.
So, it's better not to put it in.
Put cucumbers and radishes in and let
the water out.
Carrots have little water, so put a
little in.
I think one or two bites are enough.
You are kind, so I'll give you three
bites.
Is that okay?
Please put a lot of it in your mouth.
Just a little bit?
Yes, please.
I'll give you two bites.
Two bites.
This is 14.
Carrots are not moist.
Let's do the opposite.
The moisture is coming out.
Put it in the fridge.
About 30 minutes?
About 30 minutes later.
Next, I'd like to move on to the sauce.
Today, we're going to use the ultimate
sauce.
This is a sauce that you can use for the
rest of your life.
A sauce that you can use for the rest of
your life.
That's strong.
I'm sure you don't have this at home.
Oh, balsamic vinegar.
Do you know balsamic vinegar?
I know there's vinegar called balsamic
vinegar.
That's vinegar.
This is Italian.
What color is it?
Red?
Please show me.
Can you see it?
It's black.
It's a black sauce.
Two tablespoons.
One tablespoon of soy sauce.
One tablespoon.
Turn on the heat.
Medium heat.
There's something important about this.
What is it?
There's something important.
There is.
Yes.
Here's a tip for you.
Don't boil the sauce too much.
Yes.
When it's hot, it's very loose.
But when it cools down, it gets very
hard.
It gets hard.
It's flying around.
If it gets too thick, it'll be a problem
later.
I see.
I think you should boil it down to about
one-half.
Don't over-strain it.
If you say it's done, it's already a
mess.
The measurement is...
Maybe it's already half way.
It's already reduced a lot.
Slant it and slowly drip.
If you drip slowly, it will get thicker.
It's almost done.
I'll stop it.
Do you want to stop it?
Let's stop it.
Thank you.
Add 2 teaspoons of honey.
It will make it more concentrated.
Is it going to melt?
It's going to melt.
It's OK if it's mixed.
It's already...
It's already thick.
It's like caramel.
I think it's a little thick.
It's amazing.
It's perfect.
It's really thick.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Let's prepare to grill the meat.
The meat is thin today, so you don't
have to worry about it.
It's better to have a little base.
Raise the meat from here.
Cool, cool.
Now, let's move on to the opposite side.
Today's important egg liquid.
Egg liquid.
I'll make it.
Oops, it's broken.
No, no, no.
I'll mix it.
It's from Croquis.
Croquis?
No way.
What if someone says,
Give me back my egg.
Croquis.
I wish I could dig up the name.
It would be great.
It's done.
I think it's good.
And a lot of Parmigiano.
This is it.
It's a lump of umami.
It's the best.
It's easy to scrape, so be careful.
I can't move either.
It's okay to move either.
It's easier to move this way.
This is the substitute for bread crumbs.
Substitute for bread crumbs.
It's a luxury.
It's awesome.
It's expensive.
It's really expensive.
The main character is more like this
than meat.
Let's mix it with this.
It's like the egg is absorbed.
That's enough.
It's okay to put too much.
It's pretty thick.
Oh, my God.
This is awesome.
What is this dish?
Oh, my God.
I put too much.
What is this?
This is awesome.
It's okay.
This is absolutely delicious.
It's a luxury.
Oh, my God.
So, that's it for this time.
The next video will be completed.
I'm looking forward to it.
I don't know what's going to happen.
Let's enjoy the next video.
Look forward to the next video.
That's right.
It looks delicious.
It's amazing.
Are you going to run away again?
I've never eaten it before, so I'd like
to try it.
I'm looking forward to the completion
because it looks delicious from the
name.
Do you usually cook?
I don't cook much, but I've been cooking
a lot lately.
I'm making pasta.
I'm going to eat it alone.
I made Korean-style carbonara.
I'm going to look at the recipe, but I'm
going to make it properly.
I want to make it according to the
recipe.
How about you, Lisa?
I said that I was addicted to rice balls
and miso soup.
I don't usually make it myself.
I don't usually make rice balls.
I make rice with brown rice.
I freeze 100g of brown rice.
I like to put mentaiko in it.
I often put tofu and vegetables in miso
soup.
I like warm soup.
I make spicy food and consomme food.
I'm addicted to making warm soup that
goes well with brown rice.
That's great. It's like a family.
Thank you.
Hello, Stay
Next, we have a song that has been in
your heart for a long time.
Hello! Project has a lot of songs that
have been in your heart for a long time.
What is the song that has been in your
heart for a long time?
Yes, I have.
It's a solo part of Shiori Nishida's
last chorus of Yozora Niwa's song, which
is included in the fourth single of
Beyonce.
I really like the lyrics, which says,
I'm a little bit nervous.
I always perform live, and I'm a little
nervous.
I'm doing my best while thinking that
this is the point where everyone will be
nervous.
How about you, Shiori?
I'm the second B-melo of the song
Platonic Planet by Juice-Juice.
The lyrics say,
All the lyrics of Platonic Planet are
fashionable.
In the first B-melo, it says,
This planet is called this planet.
In the second B-melo, it says,
This earth is called this planet.
I think that's really nice.
It's really nice to express the feeling
of an apple falling to the ground with a
kiss.
I love the lyrics.
Hello, Project has a lot of wonderful
lyrics.
Please watch the VTR.
Please.
The song that resonates in your heart!
In this corner, we will announce the
lyrics that resonate in your heart from
the songs in Hello! Project and talk
about their charm.
I hope that the charm will be conveyed
to you who are watching Hello! Project.
This week, I, Ami Tanimoto, will
announce the lyrics.
Here it is.
I want to forget bad things. I want to
hug more than forget. I want to be
kinder tomorrow.
It's a song by Bono-san, Sorashido Ne
Ne.
I want to forget bad things, but I want
to be kinder to myself and others.
The protagonist seems to have a big
heart.
I think so too.
If you do something bad, you know what
you're doing. You know what you're doing
is bad.
So you don't do anything that people
hate.
I think that's a good thing.
I see.
I like the lyrics of this song.
The lyrics of this song are about your
own treasure.
I hate it when I have a hard time, but I
like it because it's cool to say that
it's my own treasure.
I like the lyrics of the chorus of this
song.
The lyrics of this song are about not
being weak enough to run away.
I'm clumsy, but I think that's what
links to the lyrics.
I like it. I can relate to it.
I'm fine.
Please listen to the song while watching
the lyrics.
Please look forward to the next episode.
I'm Irie Risa from JustJuice.
I'm Kokoro Maeda from Beyonce and I'm a
member of Amenomori.
Hello! Project is celebrating its 25th
anniversary this year.
On September 9th and 10th, the 25th
Anniversary Concert will be held at the
National Yogi Stadium.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. Do you have
any enthusiasm?
It's been a while since we've all
gathered as members of Hello! Project.
We've been doing solo concerts, so I'd
like to show you how we've grown.
I've never been to the National Yogi
Stadium, so I'm looking forward to
seeing the scenery from the stage.
I'd like to introduce the opening video
of the 25th anniversary of the Hello!
Project, which we chose from the 25
years of live performances.
I really like the opening video of the
concert tour 2016 Spring Concert.
I was also there when the Hello! Project
trainees were training.
Mr. Kyuto was really cool. He was
wearing a red and black dress.
I was really attracted to his mature
beauty.
I learned a lot from Mr. Kyuto, who I
was watching when I was a trainee.
I'm getting closer to Mr. Kyuto's age. I
hope I can be a woman like Mr. Kyuto.
Thank you for watching!
Hello! STAY!
Next, I'll be choosing a cool opening
for my live video.
It's the opening for the Angelm Concert
Tour 2016 Spring 9-in-1 Tamura Mayumi
Graduation Special.
I'm giving Tamura Mayumi, my senior whom
I admire, this opportunity.
I really love this concert itself.
The opening is really cool.
The members move to the music.
The performance of the Angelm is really
cool.
I love the flow from one to the next.
I think it's really cool.
I think it's really cool. I hope you
watch it.
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to make a hole in the middle
of the wall.
complete
Make a roof.
It connects the top and the bottom.
Please place wooden planks on top of the
frame.
I'll Yellow Stuffter Hieroglyphics
I'm going to make a hole in the middle
of the wall.
Complete!
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to make a new video about the
process of making a new type of
keyboard.
I'll show you how to make a new type of
Thank you for watching.
MIRACLE
UUU...
NINGNING...
warfaremen We are from the SAAR outbreak
control room, from the SAAR outbreak
control room,
Is it finished?
Just start
STRENGTHEN
Confidence
Firing
WE GON 이
WE GO theme
ONE
WE GON i
Next
Kitto Aiishita
That hug you gave me I wanted to hide
There's no way I can know
Okay, I can't wait anymore
Meet ends up loving
To be loved
I was right about that girl
I'm not good at making decisions
I was chosen, I was chosen
A happy CL toy
Only one or No.1
Each has their own reason to love
Only one and No.1
I wanted to love both of them
I couldn't do it
I want to kiss the one on the top
I couldn't steal you
Fly Fly
Hold me
Only one and No.1
Hey, hey, look ahead
I couldn't give you
Fly
I was treated kindly
I had a similar value to others
Words can't describe
My heart beats fast, I'm alone, I'm on
an adventure
My passion is against gravity
When I touch it, it's a space for just
the two of us
I chose this garden
I'm a child
I wanted to love, but I couldn't
I don't want to hurt you anymore
I couldn't steal you
Cry, cry, hold me
Only one and No.1
No, no, I can't
I couldn't even give it to you
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
give you my love
I won't kiss you, I'm fine
I love you, but it's like a lie
I hate myself
I can't get over you
Even if I say it's useless
I love you, but I can't let you go
I'm annoyed
Translated by Releska
You're cool when you're doing your best!
Hello! Project 25th Anniversary Concert
will be held on Saturday, September 9th
and Sunday, September 10th.
The 9th is a concert for the members
only, and the 10th is for the grandpas.
I think both will be fun, so please look
forward to it!
The JuiceJuice tour will start on
September 23rd. The title is JuiceJuice
10th Anniversary Concert Tour 2023 Juice
Toury.
I think it's a set list that really
feels like JuiceJuice's history, so I'm
really looking forward to it.
I think it's a set list that people who
come will definitely enjoy, so I hope
you'll come!
And BEYOND will be on September 23rd at
the TAI Japan Iconic Music Festival
2023.
It's the first time we've performed
overseas as BEYOND, so I hope many
people will come. Thank you!
And on November 15th, the Neo-Bio at
Budokan and Bio-Phonic video will be
released.
I think it's a great video, so I hope
many people will watch it!
And on September 30th, the JuiceJuice
and BEYOND will be on the Heian Jingu
Tsukiyotoyo Kyoto Neigetsu Concert 2023
Heian Jingu Tsukiyotoyo.
I can't imagine being able to hold a
concert in a wonderful place called
Heian Jingu.
I'll do my best, so I'd be happy if you
could come!
And on November 23rd, JuiceJuice will be
on the Fruit Jipper x JuiceJuice Fruit
Juice.
This is a two-man live with Fruit
Jipper, but the group itself has a
different taste.
I'm looking forward to it because it's a
precious experience because there aren't
many opportunities to do a two-man live
like JuiceJuice.
Hello! Project members will appear on
the channel.
New videos will be uploaded every
Wednesday, so please subscribe to the
channel!
This time, the guests were Iriirisato of
JuiceJuice and Kaomino of BEYOND.
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!